{
  "main": {
    "description": "I create custom solutions in JavaScript and Typescript, frequently leveraging technologies like React, Astro, and/or Next. I'm a wiz with Python, and enjoy tackling backend challenges pertaining to scalability, security, and functionality."
  },
  "about": {
    "heading": "About me",
    "blurb": "I'm a mom, partner, developer, voracious reader, and year-round grower of things.",
    "professionalDesc": "Professionally, I thrive on a diverse team of empathetic, creative, skilled devs, but also enjoy freelancing on my own, particularly when working with small local businesses.",
    "personalDesc": "Away from screens, I wrangle my toddler, play board games with my husband, care for our gardens and land, cook, and read."
  },
  "inktober": {
    "heading": "Inktober 2024"
  },
  "now": {
    "heading": "/now"
  },
  "portfolio": {
    "stayTuned": "Currently building something fun for this space!",
    "heading": "View my portfolio",
    "href": "/projects"
  },
  "contact": {
    "heading": "Talk to me!",
    "freelance": "I'm currently available for web development projects with small businesses.",
    "permanentFT": "I'm also open to exploring a remote, full-time role with your team!"
  },
  "trivia": {
    "stayTuned": "Something interactive coming to this space soon!",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "I'm studying Italian to gain citizenship through marriage",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "answer": "True! My husband is applying through family ties, but as his spouse, I need to show intermediate proficiency in the language to qualify."
      },
      {
        "question": "Our toddler sings which song daily:",
        "options": ["You Are My Sunshine", "Jingle Bells"],
        "answer": "Jingle Bells! He started singing around 12 months of age, and this was the first recognizable long-form song he latched onto."
      },
      {
        "question": "In a past job, I was:",
        "options": ["A mascot", "A chef"],
        "answer": "A mascot! Yup. A big kangaroo named K.O., mascot of the Brockton Rox (unaffiliated professional baseball team)."
      },
      {
        "question": "You might not guess that I have solid ____ skills.",
        "options": ["Trumpet", "Minecraft"],
        "answer": "Trumpet! Prior to having our son, I played in a number of actively-gigging street bands around Greater Boston."
      },
      {
        "question": "My all-time favorite TV show is:",
        "options": ["Buffy the Vampire Slayer", "The Office"],
        "answer": "Real respect to Buffy, but The Office is my #1. It's incredible how funny and how quotable this show is. Dwight is one of my favorite fictional characters."
      },
      {
        "question": "The first concert I saw live was headlined by:",
        "options": ["Third Eye Blind", "Backstreet Boys"],
        "answer": "Third Eye Blind in Portland, ME! Openers were Our Lady Peace and Eve 6. I remember writing in my journal about how 3eb's lead singer had used 'the F word' a lot."
      },
      {
        "question": "",
        "options": ["", ""],
        "answer": ""
      },
      {
        "question": "",
        "options": ["", ""],
        "answer": ""
      },
      {
        "question": "",
        "options": ["", ""],
        "answer": ""
      },
      {
        "question": "",
        "options": ["", ""],
        "answer": ""
      }
    ]
  },
  "reading": {
    "heading": "Check out my reading adventures!"
  },
  "social": {
    "gitHub": {
      "hidden": "Maggie's GitHub profile"
    },
    "linkedIn": {
      "hidden": "Maggie's LinkedIn profile"
    },
    "resume": {
      "hidden": "Maggie's resume"
    }
  },
  "technologies": {
    "copy": "A few languages and technologies I love..."
  },
  "footer": {
    "copy": "© 2024 · The online home of Maggie Bittarelli, made possible by "
  }
}